import 'question.dart';

List <Question> questionBank = [
  Question(question: "Some cats are actually allergic to humans.", answer: false),
  Question(question: "You can lead a cow downstairs but not upstairs.", answer: true),
  Question(question: "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", answer: true),
  Question(question: "A slug's blood is green." ,answer: true),
  Question(question: '''Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was "Moon" ''' ,answer: true),
  Question(question: "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal." ,answer: false),
  Question(question: "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times." ,answer: true),
  Question(question: "In London, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are technically entitled to a state funeral, because the building is considered too sacred a place." ,answer: false),
  Question(question: "The loudest sound produced by any animal is 188 decibels. That animal is the African Elephant." ,answer: true),
  Question(question: "The total surface area of two human lungs is approximately 70 square metres." ,answer: true),
  Question(question: '''Google was originally called "Backrub".''' ,answer: false),
  Question(question: "Chocolate affects a dog's heart and nervous system; a few ounces are enough to kill a small dog." ,answer: true),
];
